[{"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Mr.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " How do you do", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " What?  I can't imagine", "docId": "Mr.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " Give it away!?  The boy must be a ni", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Oh, he's not getting away with anything", "docId": "Mr.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Can I have a month's vacation", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Can I have a month's vacation", "docId": "Mr.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "With pay", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "my friend?  Oh, yeah. Yeah. No, I didn't send it. I've got it written out, though. Here it is. ", "docId": "Mr.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Oh, sure. Sure. We don't want to fire my friend", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " Excuse me. What did you say", "docId": "Mr.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "On", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah", "docId": "Mr.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "That's very nice of Mr. my friend", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "You mean to tell me you don't carry a pocketful around with you", "docId": "Mr.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I was too", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "What's that", "docId": "Mr.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": " Prairie? Oysters", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "my friend's right. I mustn't talk to anybody", "docId": "Mr.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": " Who? Miss my friend", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I say, to most people it's a washout", "docId": "Mr.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " Now, what do you see", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "It's ridiculous for us to have to worry about a boy like that.  Look at these articles about him!", "docId": "Mr.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Who cares what you were saying to your wife", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Yeah, I know", "docId": "Mr.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "The drums. He taught me to play some", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "The drums. He taught me to play some", "docId": "Mr.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Yes. I can do", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I'm crucifying him", "docId": "Mr.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Why? Why do we have to do it", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I didn't think you could come with the party and everything", "docId": "Mr.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "You threw them out", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": " Yes, lovely. We've had a lot of nice weather lately", "docId": "Mr.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Oh yes, I think it'd be a swell night to go for a walk. A nice long one", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "Oh, yes sir", "docId": "Mr.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": " A smaller bowl of flowers", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": " Did you get that stuff I was telling you about", "docId": "Mr.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "That goo. That stuff that tastes like soap", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Yes, sir", "docId": "Mr.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "No, no children", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Where is your farm", "docId": "Mr.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "that place", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "that place north", "docId": "Mr.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "that place", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": " Since he was born", "docId": "Mr.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "He was a seve", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Your Honor, I wish to call your attention to these exhibits. Mr. my friend, do you recognize these reproductions", "docId": "Mr.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Did you make the originals of them", "qsentId": 48}]